question_data = [
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "A person can get sunburned on a cloudy day.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "The planet Mars has two moons orbiting it.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Like with the Neanderthals, Homo sapiens sapiens also interbred with the Denisovans.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "A defibrillator is used to start up a heartbeat once a heart has stopped beating.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Shrimp can swim backwards.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Scientists accidentally killed the once known world&#039;s oldest living creature, a mollusc, known to be aged as 507 years old.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the periodic table, Potassium&#039;s symbol is the letter K.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "Sound can travel through a vacuum.", "correct_answer": "False",
                                       "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The most frequent subconscious activity repeated by the human body is blinking.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "&quot;Tachycardia&quot; or &quot;Tachyarrhythmia&quot; refers to a resting heart-rate near or over 100 BPM.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
